const questions = [
    {
        question: "Which country has lost the Mens World Cup Final the most times?",
        answerList: ["a. Germany", "b. Brazil", "c. Ireland", "d. Spain"],
        correctAnswer: "a. Germany"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country will host the 2022 FIFA World Cup?",
        answerList: ["a. Fiji", "b. Denmark", "c. Sweden", "d. Qatar"],
        correctAnswer: "c. Qatar"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country won the 2018 World Cup Final?",
        answerList: ["a. Croatia", "b. France", "c. Netherlands", "d. Italy"],
        correctAnswer: "b. France"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has won the most Womens World Cup finals?",
        answerList: ["a. United States", "b. Germany", "c. Japan", "d. Norway"],
        correctAnswer: ""
    },
    {
        question: "Before 2022 - How many World Cup finals have Italy won?",
        answerList: ["a. 4", "b. 1", "c. 3", "d. 2"],
        correctAnswer: "a. 4"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year was the first Mens World Cup finals?",
        answerList: ["a. 1926", "b. 1918", "c. 1930", "d. 1934"],
        correctAnswer: "c. 1930"
    },
    {
        question: "How many unique countries have won the Womens World Cup?",
        answerList: ["a. 2", "b. 4", "c. 6", "d. 8"],
        correctAnswer: "b. 4"
    },
    {
        question: "Before 2022 - How many times have England won the world cup final?",
        answerList: ["a. 0", "b. 2", "c. 3", "d. 1"],
        correctAnswer: "d. 1"
    },
    {
        question: "During the 1986 world cup - Who scored the infamous Hand of God goal?",
        answerList: ["a. Diego Maradona", "b. Christiano Ronaldo", "c. David Beckham", "d. George Best"],
        correctAnswer: "a. Diego Maradona"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country pioneered the Viking Clap football chant?",
        answerList: ["a. Denmark", "b. Finland", "c. Norway", "d. Iceland"],
        correctAnswer: "d. Iceland"
    },
    {
        question: "Which player currently holds the record for the most goals scored in the Mens World Cup?",
        answerList: ["a. Miroslav Klose", "b. Pele", "c. Gary Lineker", "d. Ronaldo"],
        correctAnswer: "a. Miroslav Klose"
    },
    {
        question: "What year was the first Womens World cup final?",
        answerList: ["a. 1991", "b. 1995", "c. 2003", "d. 2019"],
        correctAnswer: "a. 1991"
    },
    {
        question: "During the 2006 mens final which French player headbutted the Italian Materazzi?",
        answerList: ["a. Lilian Thuram", "b. Zinedine Zidane", "c. Patrick Viera", "d. Claude Makelele"],
        correctAnswer: "b. Zinedine Zidane"
    },
    {
        question: "Which two brothers are the first to play against each other in a World Cup?",
        answerList: ["a. Neville's", "b. Toure's", "c. Boateng's", "d. De Jong's"],
        correctAnswer: "c. Boateng's"
    },
    {
        question: "How many unique countries have won the Mens World Cup?",
        answerList: ["a. 6", "b. 7", "c. 8", "d. 9"],
        correctAnswer: "d. 9"
    },
    {
        question: "How many unique times have the United States won the Womens World Cup?",
        answerList: ["a. 4", "b. 7", "c. 1", "d. 3"],
        correctAnswer: "a. 4"
    },
    
]